College of Arts and Sciences Collection, 1937-1973
University of Houston Libraries
- Subject Files (Box 1-29)
  - Gulf Universities Research Corporation, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Gupta, Satish, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hagelman, Charles W., Jr., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Harvard University, 1959-1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Headstart Project, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1966-1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Hebrew Studies, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Herman Hospital, 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - High School Principles and Superintendents, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hilton Hotels, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Hirsch, General Maurice, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - History Department, 1955-1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - History Department, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - History Ph.D. Program, 1958-1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - History - University of Houston, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Hobbs, Dr. Gloria L., 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Hogg Foundation for Mental Health, 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Hogg, Miss Ima, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Home Economics - BA Proposal, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Home Economics Building (New), 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Home Economics Building (New) (Plans), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Home Economics Building Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Home Economics Department, September 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Home Economics Department, 1968-1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Honor Societies, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Honors Day, 1956-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Honors Program, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Honors Program, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Honors Program, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Honors Programs Advisory Committee, 1959-1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Hospital Classes, 1959-1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Management, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Hotel Rates, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Houston All-City Symphony Orchestra, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Houston Arts Festival, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Houston - City of, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Houston Community College, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Houston Council of Teachers of Foreign Language, 1958-1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Houston Endowment, Inc., 1958-1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Houston Municipal Art Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Houston Public Library, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Houstonian, 1955-1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Human Resources, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Hyer, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Immigration Rules, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Indiana University, 1959-1968 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Industrial Engineering, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Urban Studies (Advisory Committee), 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Institute of International Education, 1955-1971 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Institute on Urban Affairs, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Institutional Memberships, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Institutional Studies, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Instituto de Cultura Hispanica, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Instructional Television, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Insurance, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Insurance, Long Term Disability, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Interdepartmental Committee on Linguistics, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Inter-group Relations, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1958-1970 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - International Affairs, 1966-1972 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - International Affairs - The Bridge, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - International Affairs - Council on, 1965-1970 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - International Roster, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - International Student Office, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Jacksonsville University Self-study, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Jamison, Bill, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Community Center, 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Johnny George Theatre, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Junior College Conference, 1960-1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Junior Colleges, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Jury Service, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Kaplan Awards, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kettering Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - KHOU - TV Channel 11, 1964-1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Koblar, Otmar, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - KUHT - TV Operations, 1965-1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Laboratories - Science Teaching, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Laboratory Fee Under State Support, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - L'Alliance Franciase De Houston, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Lamar Tech, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Lantz, Harry, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Latin American Studies, 1954-1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Latin American Studies, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Latin American Trip, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Law Enforcement, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Lecture Series Board, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Lecturers, 1965-1969 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Requirements, Government and History, 1955-1959 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Library, 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Library, 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Library Funds - College of Arts and Sciences, 1963-1970 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Linguistics, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Loans and Scholarships - General, 1953-1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Los Alamos Laboratory - Lecturers, etc., 1956-1969 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Lunar Science Consortium, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Lunar Science Institute, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - M. D. Anderson Professorships, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Maintenance Building - Renovation, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Major Medical Insurance, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Major Roster, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Maps, 1952-1971 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Management Information Systems Committees, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Marine and Coastal Environment Council, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1960-1968 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Master of Arts in Teaching (M.A.T.), 1958-1964 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Master of Public Administration (MPA), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Master's Degree, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Mathematics by Television, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Math-Computer Sciences Faculty, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Mathematics Department, 1966-1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Mathematics Department, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Mathematics Department Statistics, 1963-1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Mathematics Engineering, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics - Ph.D. Program, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Maxwell Paintings, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - McElhinney, C. F., 1953-1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - McLendon, Will L. (Article by), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Medical Center, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Medical Students, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Medical Technology, 1960-1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Notices, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Resolutions, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Mental Retardation Center, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Mexican-American Research Center, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Mexican-American Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Military Science, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Military Science, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Military Science, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Minutes - Faculty Arts and Sciences Meetings, 1958-1972 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - MLA Newspaper, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Modern Language Association, 1955-1962 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Modern Language Association, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Modern Language Association, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Modern Language Association, 1967-1972 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Music Contracts, 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Music Department, 1951-1955 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Music Department, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Music Department, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Music Department, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Music Department, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Music Department Advisory Committee, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Music Departmental Five Year Plan, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Music Education, 1952-1967 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Music Educators National Conference Grant, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Music Guild, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Music, School of, 1959-1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Music, School of, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Music, School of, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Music, School of, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NASA - General, 1962-1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NASA Training Grants, 1963-1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - National Association of Doctors in U.S., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - National Association of State University and Land Grant Colleges, 1964-1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teachers, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - National Council of Teachers of English, 1963-1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - National Defense Educational Bill, 1958-1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities Act of 1965, 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - National German Contest for High School Students, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 1965-1972 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - National Merit Participants, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - National Opera Association, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - National Science Foundation, 1957-1969 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - National Science Foundation, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - National Science Foundation Academic Year Institute, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) Departmental Developmental Grant, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - National Science Foundation Fellowships, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, Matching Grants, 1962-1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - National Science Teachers Association, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National Security Agency, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - National Student Association, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - National Teacher Examinations, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Naval ROTC (Rice University), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - NDEA - Division of Higher Education, 1965-1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - NDEA, NSF, NASA Traineeships, 1963-1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Nepotism, 1962-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - New College, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - New College, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - New College, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - New College, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - New Faculty List - Arts and Science, UH, 1962-1971 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - New Faculty Orientation, 1958-1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - New Student Handbook, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - News Service, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - North Texas State University, 1965-1968 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Notables Books Council, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Notary Public, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Noth, Dr. Ernest Erich, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Notices to the Department Chairman, 1958-1961 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Nursery School, 1944-1959 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Nursery School, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Nursery School, 1964-1973 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Nurses - Bachelor of Science for, 1959-1965 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Oath of Allegiance, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Odessa College, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Offerings for Adults in College of Arts and Science, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Offers to Faculty Members, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Office Hours, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Office Management - Rooms 108 and 110, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Office of Administration, 1963-1969 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Office of International Affairs, 1961-1969 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Office of International Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Oklahoma State University, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - O'Leary Endowment, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Oliver, 1st Lt. Kenneth G., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1959-1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Ong, Walter J., S.J. (St. Louis University), 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Open University, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Optional Retirement Program, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Organ, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Organization Chart, College of Arts and Sciences, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Organization for Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Organization of University, 1962-1967 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Orientation, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Osborne, Bill, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Osteopathy and Surgery, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Otero, Hector, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Outstanding Educators of America, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Outterson, John, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Pakistan Project, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Pan American Petroleum Corporation, 1960-1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Pantillon, Georges-Henri, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Parents' Convocation, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Parking Facilities, 1967-1973 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Patent Policy, 1967-1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Pay Scales, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Payro, Professor Julio E., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Payroll, 1953-1969 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Payroll Procedures, 1961-1971 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Peabody Carnegie Graduate Fellowship, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Perennial Students, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Personnel, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Personnel Evaluations, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Personnel Plans, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Personnel Psychology Services Departmental Five Year Plan, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Personnel Services, Office of, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Petroleum Symposium, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1953-1964 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Phillips, Ellis L. Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Philosophical Library, Inc., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Philosophy and Religion Department, 1953-1969 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Photography Courses and Equipment, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Photography Department, 1954-1959 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Photography Equipment - Disposal of, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Physical Plant, 1959-1968 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Physics - Advanced Degrees Completed, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Physics Department, 1956-1965 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Physics Department, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Physics Department, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Physics Ph.D. Program, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Pi Kappa Delta, Inactive, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Piper Professorships, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Pipkin, James H., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Pitzer, Kenneth, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Placement Center, 1966-1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Planning Committee - University, 1962-1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Planning - Five-Year Institutional, Spring 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Planning Procedures, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Planning Study, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Planning Study, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Pogue, Mrs. Shirley May Wewar, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Policy Committee, 1959-1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Political Administration, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Political Science - Advanced Degrees Complete, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Political Science - Advanced Degrees Pending, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Political Science Department, 1964-1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Political Science Ph.D. Program, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Political Science Ph.D. Program, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Population Program, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Post-Graduate Classification, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Posting Regulations, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Potter, Robert W., 1958 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Poverty Programs, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Power Plant, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Prairie View, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Pre-medical and Pre-dental Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Pre-medical Program, 1956-1969 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Presbyterian Faculty Fellowship, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Presidential Committee on Science, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - President's Fund Council, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - President's Inauguration, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Princeton University, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Probation and Suspension, Committee On, 1958-1968 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Professional Placement Service State Department, 1963-1967 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Program Council Forum Committee, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Program for the Blind, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Program Planning and Development, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Project Headstart, May 1965-July 1966 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Project Headstart, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Promotion Recommendations, 1956-1966 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Promotions, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Proposals, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Psychology, September 1960-August 1966 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Psychology - Advanced Degrees Completed (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
    - A-C, 1964-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - D-J, 1964-1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - K-M, 1963-1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - N-S, 1964-1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - T-Z, 1964-1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Psychology Clinic, 1967-1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Psychology Clinical Appointments, 1966-1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Psychology Clinical Appointments, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Psychology Department, 1953-1958 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Psychology Department, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Psychology Department, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Psychology Department, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Public Colleges, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Public Services Careers, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Publications Committee, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Publications - General, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Purchasing Department, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Purchasing Procedures, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Quality Point Average, 1954-1968 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Radiation Safety Officer, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Radio - TV Department, 1954-1962 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Re-admission From Suspension, 1959-1970 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Recommendations (Until Summer 1962), 1954-1962 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Recruiting, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Recruiting Practices, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Registrar, 1945-1961 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Registrar - Letters From, 1954-1957 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Registrar Statistics, 1963-1972 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Registrar's Annual Report, 1962-1968 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Registrar's Annual Report, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Registrar's Office - Correspondence with, 1961-1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Registration Information, 1967-1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Registration Statistics, 1958-Summer 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Religion Major, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Religious Activities, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Religious Center, 1958-1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Religious Courses in a State University, 1962-1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Religious Emphasis, 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Religious Studies Program, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Remedial Courses in the Sciences, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Requisitions, A and S, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Requisitions, FY, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Research - Computing Sciences (Organic), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Research Grants - Biology, 1958-1964 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Research Grants - Chemistry, 1958-1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Research Grants - English, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Research Grants - General, 1958-1970 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Research Grants - Geology, 1958-1966 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Research Grants - History, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Research Grants - Physics, 1963-1972 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Research Grants - Psychology (Evans), 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Research Grants - Psychology General, 1958-1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Research Grants - Psychology (Meyerson), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Research Grants - Psychology (Shapiro), 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Research Grants - Psychology (Sheer), 1963-1966 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Research Grants - Psychology (Stovall), 1958-1964 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Research Grants - Psychology (Vineberg), 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Research Grants - Speech and Hearing Therapy, 1964-1970 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Research Initiation Grants, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Research Institutes - U. of H., 1955-1957 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Research Inventory, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Research Leaves, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Research - Office of, 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Research - Office of, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Research Proposals, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Research - Themis Project, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Research - Unallocated Funds, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Reservations, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC), 1956 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Retired Professors Registry, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Retirement, 1937-1969 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Revenue Figures - College of Arts and Sciences, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Rhodes Scholarship, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Rice University, 1954-1968 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Rider, John A. Memorial Book Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Rienzi Foundation, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Robinson, Francis, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1965-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, John D. III Fund, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Role and Scope, 1962-1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Rotary Foundation Fellowship, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Royalties - Policy on, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Roy Cullen Building, 1966-1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Rubens, Peter Paul, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Rubloff, Arthur, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ruchelman, Maryon W., Ph.D., Endocrinology, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Sabbatical Leaves, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - S. A. Essay, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Safety - General, 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Salaries, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Salary Supplementation University Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Saunders, Mrs. Edna, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Scanlan, Robert H., 1959 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Schedule Hours, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, 1955-1961 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, 1962-1965 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Schindler, Dali, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Scholar Program, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship and Auditions Committee, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Scholarships and Donations (Box 22, Folder 24-32)
    - Art, 1965-1971 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Communication Arts, 1962-1965 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Drama, 1964-1970 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Foreign Languages, 1962-1970 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - General, 1963-1972 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Home Economics, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Music and Band, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Music and Band, 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Psychology, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Scholastic Aptitude Tests, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Scholastic Requirements - Committees on, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Science and Engineering - Proposed Merger of, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Science and Research Building, 1964-1969 (Box 22, Folder 36)